/*jshint esversion: 6 */

/** Science quiz section */
/** Science section questions */
// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let quizQuestions = {
    type: [
        {
            science: [
                {
                    numb: 1,
                    question: "Eating what is important for your health?",
                    answer: "A Balanced Diet",
                    options: [ "Sugars", "Carbohydrates", "A Balanced Diet", "Junk Food" ]
                },
                {
                    numb: 2,
                    question: "How many food groups are there in a balanced diet?",
                    answer: "Five",
                    options: [ "Five", "Six", "Seven", "Ten" ]
                },
                {
                    numb: 3,
                    question: "What are building blocks for the body because they help it grow and repair itself?",
                    answer: "Protein",
                    options: [ "Carbohydrates", "Protein", "Fruits and Vegetables", "Dairy Products" ]
                },
                {
                    numb: 4,
                    question: "Which products are important because they keep your bones and teeth healthy?",
                    answer: "Dairy Products",
                    options: [ "Protein", "Carbohydrates", "Dairy Products", "Fruits and Vegetables" ]
                },
                {
                    numb: 5,
                    question: "What are full of health-boosting vitamins, antioxidants and fibre?",
                    answer: "Fruits and Vegetables",
                    options: [ "Dairy Products", "Carbohydrates", "Fruits and Vegetables", "Protein" ]
                },
                {
                    numb: 6,
                    question: "Too much of which food group can damage your teeth or make you gain weight?",
                    answer: "Fats and Sugars",
                    options: [ "Dairy Products", "Carbohydrates", "Fruits and Vegetables", "Fats and Sugars" ]
                },
            ],
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            geography : [
                {
                    numb: 1,
                    question: "In a Compass, what does \'N'\ stand for?",
                    answer: "North",
                    options: [ "Nice", "North", "New", "November" ]
                },
                {
                    numb: 2,
                    question: "In a Compass, what does \'S'\ stand for?",
                    answer: "South",
                    options: [ "Sea", "Sun", "South", "Survive" ]
                },
                {
                    numb: 3,
                    question: "In a Compass, what does \'E'\ stand for?",
                    answer: "East",
                    options: [ "Eat", "Earth", "Enjoy","East" ]
                },
                {
                    numb: 4,
                    question: "In a Compass, what does \'W'\ stand for?",
                    answer: "West",
                    options: [ "Wind", "West", "Winter","Wild" ]
                },
                {
                    numb: 5,
                    question: "In a Compass, what does \'NW'\ stand for?",
                    answer: "North-West",
                    options: [ "Not-Well", "North-West", "November","New-Vine" ]
                },
                {
                    numb: 6,
                    question: "In a Compass, what does \'NE'\ stand for?",
                    answer: "North-East",
                    options: [ "Never-Eat", "Near", "Never","North-East" ]
                },
                {
                    numb: 7,
                    question: "In a Compass, what does \'SW'\ stand for?",
                    answer: "South-West",
                    options: [ "Sea-Wind", "Sun-Worthy", "South-Wast", "Sun-white" ]
                },
                {
                    numb: 8,
                    question: "In a Compass, what does \'SE'\ stand for?",
                    answer: "South-East",
                    options: [ "Sea-Entry", "Sun-Escapes", "South-East", "South-Entry" ]
                },
            ],
        }
    ]:
    [
        {
            maths : [
                {
                    numb: 1,
                    question: "What is 4 multipled by 4?",
                    answer: "16",
                    options: [ "12", "14", "16", "18"]
                },
                {
                    numb: 2,
                    question: "What is 4 multipled by 6?",
                    answer: "24",
                    options: [ "24", "34", "16", "18"]
                },
                {
                    numb: 3,
                    question: "What is 4 multipled by 2?",
                    answer: "8",
                    options: [ "4", "6", "10", "8"]
                },
                {
                    numb: 4,
                    question: "What is 4 multipled by 5?",
                    answer: "20",
                    options: [ "20", "24", "16", "18"]
                },
                {
                    numb: 5,
                    question: "What is 4 multipled by 10?",
                    answer: "40",
                    options: [ "10", "40", "20", "44"]
                },
                {
                    numb: 6,
                    question: "What is 4 multipled by 8?",
                    answer: "32",
                    options: [ "32", "34", "36", "38"]
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
};